RAHUL SHARMA

SUMMARY

Software Engineer with 8+ years of background in creating and executing innovative software solutions to enhance business productivity. 4+ years of experience with Apttus CPQ/CLM products and experience in all aspects of salesforce development and integration.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Consultant

Deloitte India | Pune, India | March 2022 - Current

- Worked on Apttus callback classes to implement pricing scenarios and validations
- Worked on Apttus approvals and Lightning web components.

Senior Consultant

Apttus | Ahmedabad, India | August 2018 - March 2022

- Communicate and identify product demo requirements from an on-site sales engineer.
- Provide build/backend support to onsite sales engineer.
- Design & implement salesforce out of the box and custom solutions to meet client needs

Software Engineer

Tatvasoft | Ahmedabad, India | September 2017 - August 2018

- Worked as a developer on a variety of frameworks and technologies including MVC, 2 Tier architecture, 3 Tier architecture, Angular JS, Angular 2, Node JS.
- Participated in SQL Server database design and implementation.

Business Model Engineer

Stayinfront India | Gandhinagar, India | June 2015 - September 2017

- Worked with the product development team in the feature implementation as well as maintenance activities.
- Designed & implemented features using VBScript, ASP.Net, C# and Javascript.

EDUCATION

B.E. (Computer Science) | Parul Institute Of Engineering And Technology | 7.10 CPI

Gujarat Technological University, Vadodara

March 2015

HSC | Shree Narayan Vidyalaya | 67%

Gujarat Higher Secondary Education Board, Vadodara

SSC | Sardar Vallabhbhai Vidyalaya | 83.34%

Gujarat Secondary Education Board, Vadodara March 2009

CONTACT

9 9722307329

rs30081994@gmail.com

Vadodara, India 390025

linkedin.com/in/rasharma94

SKILLS

Technology Skills

- Apttus CPQ/CLM
- Conga

Composer/Grid/Sign/Orchestrate

- Salesforce Development
- Apex
- Visualforce
- · Lightning Development
- · Integration
- SOAP/REST API

CERTIFICATIONS

- Apttus CPQ
- Apttus CLM
- Quote-to-Cash
- Conga Sign
- Conga Grid

LANGUAGES

Gujarati: First Language

Hindi: C2

Proficient (C2)

English: C2

Proficient (C2)